

David Jin (LungGuo Jin) SOFTWARE ENGINERR

- pinefirst@outlook.com
- pinefirst
- https://github.com/pinefirst
- https://pinefirst.github.io/
- 13591411719
- 30th Nov, 1989
- Language: EN, CN
- Kowloon, HK
- linkedin.com/in/tiger-dev

Education

Jilin University

Jilin – 2008-2011

Bachelor of Science:

Computer Science And Programming

Skills

- Blockchain
- Solidity, Web3.js, Ethereum
- HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrp
- PHP. Laravel, Codelgniter
- JavaScript
- ReactJs, Next.JS
- Angular
- Vue, Nuxt
- Gatsby
- Nest.JS
- Typescript
- Tailwind CSS
- Node.JS, Express
- MySql, MongoDB, PostgreSql
- RestfulAPI, GraphQL
- Electron
- Android(Jana,Kotlin)
- Hybrid(ReactNative,Flutter)
- Github, Jira





Professional Summary

I have been specializing in web & mobile for 9++years and worked. Also I have been focus on Blockchain.

With individuals and several companies.

and always focus on customer satisfaction.

My goal is to take your vision and help you bring it to life.

You may have never worked with developers before or understand one line of code but that's not a problem.

My clear communication style, expert development knowledge, experience in developer management, and results-oriented work ethic, will help get you to an MVP/Beta launch in the quickest amount of time without breaking the bank. We take the time, stress, and energy out of launching your project

Work History



Front-End Developer

10/2011 - 10/2015

Shenyang Worldward Informations Technology Co.Ltd

Working as a Front-end lead for the product based company to build a scalable, secure and user-friendly product for the clients Taking part in building ecommerce websites using PHP, Laravel, Cl.



Senior Web Developer

10/2015 - 01/2020

Putian Yitong Technology Co.Ltd

Built number of websites and mobile using various kinds of language and AWS Worked with direct client to understand their business requirements and gathered required information for development.

Helped build and enhance highly available, scalable, real-time and secure systems used by customers worldwide.

Converted PSD mockups into pure hand-written HTML5 and CSS pages.

Follow best practices and standards for accessibility and cross-browser compatibility. Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability

Adhered to high-quality development standards while delivering solutions on-time and on-budget

Freelacing- Self Employed



Get and Manage task from client

Developed dynamic and interactive website that ensured high traffic, page views and user experience, resulting in 30% increase in profits.

Fixed buds from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed



Grade Arc

01/2020 - 12/2021

01/2022 - current Manage front-end on project

